cpaonline.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Find Accounting Software

Find Accounting Software is committed to protecting the privacy of our visitor's personally identifiable information. To better protect our users, we openly provide our information handling practices as listed below.

## Types of Data collected

Among the types of Personal Data that this Application collects, by itself or through third parties, there are: Cookie, Usage Data, First Name, Last Name, Phone number, Company name, Profession, Email and ZIP/Postal code.

Other Personal Data collected may be described in other sections of this privacy policy or by dedicated explanation text contextually with the Data collection. The Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or collected automatically when using this Application. Any use of Cookies - or of other tracking tools - by the Application or by the owners of third party services used by this Application, unless stated otherwise, serves to identify Users and remember their preferences, for the sole purpose of providing the service required by the User. Failure to provide certain Personal Data may make it impossible for this Application to provide its services.

The User assumes responsibility for the Personal Data of third parties published or shared through this Application and declares to have the right to communicate or broadcast them, thus relieving the Data Controller of all responsibility.

## Mode and place of processing the Data

### Method of processing

The Data Controller processes the Data of Users in proper manner and shall take appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification or unauthorized destruction of the Data. Access to the Data may be available to Data Processors such as employees involved with the processing or to external parties providing services to the Data Controller, third party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communication agencies. The updated list of these parties may be requested from the Data Controller at any time.

### Place

The Data is processed at the Data Controller headquarters, unless stated otherwise in the rest of this document.

### Conservation Time

The Data is kept for the time necessary to provide the service requested by the User, or stated by the purposes outlined in this document, and the User can always request the Data Controller for their suspension or removal.

## The use of the collected Data

The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Application to provide its services, as well as for the following purposes: Analytics, Contacting the User, Advertising, Remarketing and Behavioral Targeting, Content performance and features testing (A/B testing) and Interaction with external social networks and platforms.

The Personal Data used for each purpose is outlined in the specific sections of this document.

## Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data

Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services:

  1. ### Advertising

These services allow User Data to be utilized for advertising communication purposes displayed in the form of banners and other advertisements on this Application, possibly based on User interests. This does not mean that all Personal Data are used for this purpose. Information and conditions of use are shown below. Some of the services listed below may use Cookies to identify Users or they may use the behavioral retargeting technique, i.e. displaying ads tailored to the Userâ€™s interests and behavior, including those detected outside this Application. For more information, please check the privacy policies of the relevant services.

    * #### AdRoll (Semantic Sugar, Inc.)

AdRoll is an advertising service provided by Semantic Sugar, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.

Place of processing: USA â€“ [Privacy Policy](http://www.adroll.com/about/privacy)

  2. ### Analytics

The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.

    * #### Google Analytics (Google)

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (â€œGoogleâ€). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Application, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.

Place of processing: USA â€“ [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

  3. ### Contacting the user

By filling in the contact form with their Data, the Users authorizes this Application to use these details to reply to requests for information, quotes or any other kind of request as indicated by the formâ€™s header.

Personal Data collected: Company name, Email, First Name, Last Name, Phone number, Profession and ZIP/Postal code.

  4. ### Content performance and features testing (A/B testing)

The services contained in this section allow the Owner to track and analyze the User response concerning web traffic or behavior regarding changes to the structure, text or any other component of this Application.

    * #### Optimizely (Optimizely, Inc.)

Optimizely is an A/B testing service provided by Optimizely, Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.

Place of processing: USA â€“ [Privacy Policy](http://www.optimizely.com/privacy)

  5. ### Interaction with external social networks and platforms

These services allow interaction with social networks or other external platforms directly from the pages of this Application. The interaction and information obtained by this Application are always subject to the Userâ€™s privacy settings for each social network. If a service enabling interaction with social networks is installed it may still collect traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.

    * #### Facebook Like button and social widgets (Facebook)

The Facebook Like button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Facebook social network provided by Facebook Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.

Place of processing: USA â€“ [Privacy Policy](http://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation.php)

    * #### Google+ +1 button and social widgets (Google)

The Google+ +1 button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Google+ social network provided by Google Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.

Place of processing: USA â€“ [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

    * #### Linkedin button and social widgets (Linkedin)

The Linkedin button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Linkedin social network provided by Linkedin Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.

Place of processing: USA â€“ [Privacy Policy](http://www.linkedin.com/static?key=privacy_policy&trk=hb_ft_priv)

    * #### Twitter Tweet button and social widgets (Twitter)

The Twitter Tweet button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Twitter social network provided by Twitter Inc.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.

Place of processing: USA â€“ [Privacy Policy](http://twitter.com/privacy)

  6. ### Remarketing and Behavioral Targeting

These services allow this Application and its partners to inform, optimize and serve advertising based on past use of this Application by the User. This activity is performed by tracking Usage Data and by using Cookies, information that is transferred to the partners that manage the remarketing and behavioral targeting activity.

    * #### AdWords Remarketing (Google)

AdWords Remarketing is a Remarketing and Behavioral Targeting service provided by Google Inc. that connects the activity of this Application with the Adwords advertising network and the Doubleclick Cookie

For the opt-out: <http://google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en>

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.

Place of processing: USA â€“ [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

    * #### Google Analytics for Display Advertisers (Google)

Google Analytics for Display Advertisers is a Remarketing and Behavioral Targeting service provided by Google Inc. that connects the tracking activity performed by Google Analytics and its Cookies with the Adwords advertising network and the Doubleclick Cookie.

For the opt-out: <http://google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en>.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.

Place of processing: USA â€“ [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

## Additional information about Data collection and processing

### Legal Action

The User's Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Data Controller, in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of this Application or the related services.

### Additional Information about User's Personal Data

In addition to the information in this privacy policy, this Application may provide the User with contextual information concerning particular services or the collection and processing of Personal Data.

### System Logs and Maintenance

For operation and maintenance purposes, this Application and any third party services may collect files that record interaction with this Application (System Logs) or use for this purpose other Personal Data (such as IP Address).

### Information not contained in this policy

More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Data Controller at any time at its contact information.

### The rights of Users

Users have the right, at any time, to know whether their Personal Data has been stored and can consult the Data Controller to learn about their contents and origin, to verify their accuracy or to ask for them to be supplemented, cancelled, updated or corrected, or for their transformation into anonymous format or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any and all legitimate reasons. Requests should be sent to the Data Controller at the contact information set out above.

### Changes to this privacy policy

The Data Controller reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom. If a User objects to any of the changes to the Policy, the User must cease using this Application and can request the Data Controller to erase the Personal Data. Unless stated otherwise, the then-current privacy policy applies to all Personal Data the Data Controller has about Users.

### Information about this privacy policy

The Data Controller is responsible for this privacy policy, prepared starting from the modules provided by Iubenda

## Definitions and legal references

### Personal Data (or Data)

Any information regarding a natural person, a legal person, an institution or an association, which is, or can be, identified, even indirectly, by reference to any other information, including a personal identification number.

### Usage Data

Information collected automatically from this Application (or third party services employed in this Application ), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use this Application, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server's answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Application) and the details about the path followed within the Application with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User's IT environment.

### User

The individual using this Application, which must coincide with or be authorized by the Data Subject, to whom the Personal Data refer.

### Data Subject

The legal or natural person to whom the Personal Data refers to.

### Data Processor

The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization authorized by the Data Controller to process the Personal Data in compliance with this privacy policy.

### Data Controller (or Application Owner, or Owner)

The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization with the right, also jointly with another Data Controller, to make decisions regarding the purposes, and the methods of processing of Personal Data and the means used, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of this Application. The Data Controller, unless otherwise specified, is the Owner of this Application.

### This Application

The hardware or software tool by which the User Personal Data is collected.

### Cookie

Small piece of data stored in the User's device.

### Legal information

Notice to European Users: this privacy statement has been prepared in fulfillment of the obligations under Art. 10 of EC Directive n. 95/46/EC, and under the provisions of Directive 2002/58/EC, as revised by Directive 2009/136/EC, on the subject of Cookies.

This privacy policy is solely about this Application.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions or would like more information on our privacy practices, please contact us at [privacy@findaccountingsoftware.com](mailto:privacy@findaccountingsoftware.com).

Last Updated: July 11, 2013
